Hello?
Mr. John?
How do you do, sir?
Hello?
I am good, but who's this?
Dubey.
Manoj Dubey, sir.
Remember?
I show you girls in UP?
You eat Chole-Kulcha, very spicy, sir?
Oh yeah.
Yes, of course.
Mr. Dubey, how are you?
Fantastic, sir.
So... you still in Delhi?
No, we left actually.
We're going to Rajasthan.
Okay.
Great, great.
Rajasthan is very beautiful.
Good news for you, sir.
We have some beautiful
young girls here for you.
That's nice, Mr. Dubey.
But we actually don't want your girls.
- Sorry.
- But sir, we got new stock here.
Just like you wanted.
I'm whatsapping you their pics.
You'll definitely like, sir.
Just see the pics and call me back.
Mr. Dubey, I've discussed it with my wife.
And we're gonna find our own surrogate.
Thank you, Mr. Dubey.
Sir...!
Is that the Surrogacy Clinic guy?
Yeah.
He has new girls for us.
Those girls are physically weak, John.
You've seen that place?
It's like a factory out there.
I know.
I told him,
but obviously he wants to make money.
Well, money is not the problem.
We need a young and healthy girl.
I know, honey.
I know.
We'll find her.
Sir?
Sorry?
Girl?
You want girl?
I want a girl?
Oh.
You know, you and madam... very forward.
We cannot handle one
woman and he wants two.
What, John?
Are you telling him
that you want another woman?
No, no.
Bhanu, when did I say that?
In car you both (were) talking...
Healthy and fit girl?
Oh my God, no!
Bhanu, listen,
we want a girl, but not for John.
You are quite fluent in Hindi.
I spent six years in Delhi.
I attended Hindi classes there.
Wonderful.
Then who do you need a girl for?
We need a ma for our child.
Ma?
You mean a Dayima?
What's a Dayima?
Dayima is someone who looks
after your child when you go out.
No, no, no.
We want a girl who looks
after our child, inside.
Inside?
What do you mean by inside?
In her womb.
Our child...
- Okay.
- In her womb.
We want a surrogate mother.
Because I can't conceive.
Your child in her womb?
Hmm?
I'll explain it to you, come on.
So that's how it works.
This is amazing.
We don't have kids either.
Been married 12 years.
I'll ask if she would
like to give this a try.
It's not cheap, costs millions.
Oh God.
It's not our cup of tea then.
We poor people take a loan
to educate our children,
not to have them.
What's he saying?
He's saying that he's been trying
to have a baby for a long time too.
And that he would never
be able to afford a surrogate.
No worries, ma'am.
I'll work hard
and have one naturally.
Bhanu?
- Yes?
- I'm sorry to hear that.
So you understand
what we're going through.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
So could you help us find a surrogate?
You are family, sir.
Why not?
But I am a poor guy...
Money?
Of course, we'll pay you.
How much?
Five.
That's too less, sir.
You know how expensive cooking gas is?
- At least make it ten.
- Ten?
That's a lot.
We can't afford that much.
We can only afford to give 500,000.
Bhanu?
Huh?
Five...
500,000.
For that kind of money,
even I'd agree to carry your baby.
Done, sir.
Deal.
Rajendra?
Go call her.
Move it.
Amma, come on out.
Shanu Amma.
She has had 14 kids.
Two pairs of twins.
She is quite experienced.
Best surrogate.
- Bhanu!
- Hmm?
She won't work.
Why not?
She is quite talented.
Back in the day,
she'd climb a tree in no time.
Amma, can you still climb a tree?
Yes.
Go and climb one for us.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please stop.
- Stop.
- What is happening?
Bhanu,
she cannot be our surrogate.
We want a young girl.
Young.
Not this old.
Bhanu... the surrogate doesn't decide
the look of the baby,
it decides the health.
Can you explain this to him?
We have to be safe.
One of our friends
picked a surrogate here,
but she was very weak.
So unfortunately,
the baby didn't survive.
I get it.
Amma, go inside.
I'll get you the best merch.
Merch?
Ma.
I said Ma.
Please come with me, sir.
Let's go, sir.
"Hey Bikaneri chick, you are so slick."
"Lost my house because of you,"
"And now I'm about to lose my job too."
"Hey Romeos!"
"Roadside Romeos!"
"Innocent looking deceptive..."
"liars!"
[Background vocal]
"Hey Romeos, worthless boyos!"
"Stop bothering me,
you good for nothing fellows."
"You have already stolen our hearts,"
"Don't leave us behind."
"This isn't right, my love."
"You sometimes look like Mona Lisa."
"And sometimes like a mesmerising Lolita."
"Oh."
"And sometimes like a mystery."
"You are a super-super-super
supreme beauty."
"From head to toe, an absolute beauty."
"You are a super-super-super
supreme beauty."
"Hey supreme beauty..."
[Background vocal]
"I can't be tied down."
"I am like the wild wind."
"I have a long way ahead of me."
"I am not interested in gems or jewels,"
"I am interested in chasing my dreams."
"I am used to my dreams coming true."
"I don't want men chasing me."
"I am made for the big screen."
"You have already stolen our hearts,"
"Don't leave us behind."
"This isn't right, my love."
"You sometimes look like Mona Lisa."
"Buzz off."
"And sometimes like a mesmerising Lolita."
"And sometimes like a mystery."
"You are a super-super-super
supreme beauty."
"From head to toe, an absolute beauty."
"You are a super-super-super
supreme beauty."
"Don't touch me."
"I don't want be yours."
"I don't care even
if you beg for my company."
"No, no, no..."
"Hey Bikaneri chick, you are so slick."
"Lost my house because of you,"
"And now I'm about to lose my job too."
"Looking at your curves,"
"My heart starts to race."
"Like the hands of a clock
going hickory, dickory, dockery."
"No, no, no..."
Owner's car...
driver's sweat...
makes the journey heartfelt.
Cheers.
Hey, Jolly Bro!
How are you?
When are you coming here?
It will take some time, Bro.
How much time are we talking about, huh?
Thousands of girls folk to
Mumbai every day to become a star.
The more you delay the
slimmer your chances get.
I need to have enough dough to come there.
You need to hurry up, girl.
I had a word with Dabboo,
he takes 500,000 for a photo shoot.
Excluding costume and makeup.
500,000?
For a photo shoot?
Does he do with a camera made of gold?
He's the most sought after
photographer in Bollywood.
How about we first shoot
a music video instead then?
We'll make it go viral.
It won't cost you much.
Just about need a million, yeah?
I'll have a word with Bhushan.
Jolly?
You're at a shoot!
Who was that?
Hello?
Sounded like he was
speaking to Shah Rukh Khan.
- Really?
- Really.
What was Jolly saying?
How much I have managed.
How can I possibly achieve
my dream with this, Shama?
Just have patience.
Patience bears fruits.
I've been dieting
on patience for years now.
Bhanu.
Sir.
I was saying my evening prayers.
What is it?
Bhanu, we have something
we'd like to tell you.
Yes?
Honey..
We liked a girl.
We want someone like
her to be our surrogate.
Who is this girl?
Who? Who?
Well, she's beautiful,
she's tall and she's a dancer.
Oh, the tall girl who
was dancing downstairs?
Why didn't I think of her?
If we could get someone like her...?
Why someone like her?
We can get her.
Really?
Is that possible?
Yes, of course.
You are family.
Keep the money ready.
- Money can buy everything.
- What is happening?
- He's saying that he thinks may be able to get--
- Sir?
How much do you plan on paying her?
Money?
How many times do I have
to tell you to hurry up?
We won't find a ride home now.
We will.
Give me the money.
Here.
Let's go.
No, I can talk.
Bhanu Pratap, an art lover.
That was an amazing performance.
- My God!
- Thanks.
How are you guys going home?
By rickshaw?
If we get one.
You'll take a rickshaw?
Such a big star will travel in a rickshaw?
I cannot let that happen.
How will I face the society?
How will I face God?
Not possible.
Well, this is the only you have,
So there is no other option.
Your friend is so funny.
Come, let me drop you home in my taxi.
You own a taxi?
- Yes.
- How much will you charge us?
Come on,
how can I take money from you?
I am an art lover.
I am your fan.
A big fan.
- No thank you, we'll manage.
- No.
He's a fan.
We cannot refuse him.
Give me the rickshaw fare.
- Let's go.
- Yes, you shouldn't break your fan's heart.
- Let me carry your bag.
- No, I can manage.
My taxi's parked right outside.
You gave a mind-blowing performance.
"I learnt to walk holding your hand."
"I thrived under your care."
"Mother!"
"Oh my mother..."
Mother! Oh my mother!
A mother God's best gift to mankind.
Don't you think?
Right.
A mother-child relationship,
is the most pious
one in the world.
Looks like you love your mother a lot.
A lot.
- What's her name?
- Kainkayi.
You don't say!
And you still love her?
Love her?
I owe my life to her.
She nurtured me in
her womb for nine months.
Being a mother
is the greatest gift on earth.
If I could,
I would carry a child myself.
And where would
the baby come out from?
The rare end?
That's the problem with men.
We cannot give birth.
What should I do?
Take a right and drop me home.
Then do whatever you please.
You can pull up here.
Bye.
You have the dagger, right?
- Hmm?
- You have the dagger, right?
Yes, I do. I have the dagger.
Call once you reach home.
I'll call you.
- Good night.
Step on it.
Drive!
Pull up here.
- Here?
- Yes.
Excuse me?
What's wrong?
Did I forget something?
No, you didn't.
Well--
Well, like I said, being a
mother is the greatest gift on earth.
So what does that have to do with me?
I hope your dagger isn't too sharp.
Should I chop something off?
Something?
Anything you want.
No, thank you.
What were you saying?
Come on, tell me.
What is it?
Well...
You have something that men don't.
A womb.
The place where babies grow.
Are you drunk?
No.
I did have just a bit.
- Bloody drunkard.
- Please hear me out.
The American couple
staying at the Amar Mahal?
Did you see them?
No.
I'll introduce you to them tomorrow.
They... like you.
They want you to have their baby.
Because you are a dancer.
You have a great body.
God has blessed you with great features.
Who was that?
No one!
"Oh my beloved..."
Saw the number of
likes on my FB, hmm?
855 likes.
I am sure it'll reach 1000 by tomorrow.
Just read the comments.
"Hot!"
"Set fire to the rain!"
I have quite a fan following out here.
Call me to Bombay already, my Romeo!
Hot!
Let me go you bandit!
You're crazy!
My bad luck is your good luck, girls.
You will be out of jobs once I get there.
No one will even think about you.
All the heroes will
chase me screaming Mimi-Mimi.
I am coming!
Wrong scale, Dad.
You should pick a higher scale.
Now you'll teach me about music, huh?
Isn't she a part of your lineage, uncle?
Hello!
I have my own identity.
I have done 72 shows.
How many, kids?
72.
Right.
Her videos are on FB, you know?
Sis, what's the name
of the magazine that you read?
Cosmopolitan.
You wouldn't read this nonsense
if you would have finished college.
Mind your own business, Mom.
I know what I want from life.
Why don't you enlighten me?
What do you want from life?
Mr. Jadawat's daughter
got married at the age of 21.
And this one.
There! That's where they go wrong, Aatif.
They just don't get it.
PC wouldn't be a star
if her parents hadn't encouraged her.
PC?
Priyanka Chopra, Uncle.
Went from Bareilly to Bollywood
and became a star.
But her father was a doctor
in the army,
not some ordinary Joe.
Come here.
Who did you call an ordinary Joe, huh?
You.
Tell me something,
how do you know all this?
Social network, Uncle.
I am telling you!!!
You should open
an account with Facebook.
It only costs 200 bucks.
Think again.
Facebook?
I think you've dropped your money.
Someone stole your sandals.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
Auntie, your veil's sweeping the floor.
Yours' too.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Priest!
I hope you are putting
in a good word for me.
I come twice a week these days.
I had a word with God.
Asked Him to bless you
with a handsome husband,
and a beautiful child.
You don't say!
No wonder it is taking so long!
That's not what I want.
I want to go to Bollywood.
Where's that?
A wrong priest can mess up your plans.
You should reconsider, auntie.
[Prayers]
Hey!
Put it on my tab.
Give me the plate.
Put that on my tab as well.
Does she come here every day?
Mimi ji?
Can I have a minute, Mimi ji?
What is it?
Why are you following me?
Do you want another slap?
Or my sandal?
Please hear me out.
Then beat me or slap me.
Look, I'm offering you my other cheek.
Please, just hear me out.
Fine, out with it.
You slapped me for no reason.
For no reason?
You asked me to sleep
with that foreigner.
You should thank God
I only slapped you.
Where I am from,
we usually smash faces.
For no reason he says!
You misunderstand.
You don't have to sleep
with John to have his baby.
He won't even touch you.
No physical contact.
Are you drunk again?
Mimi ji, this is a new method.
It's called surrogacy.
What? Legacy?
Not legacy.
Let me explain.
Do you own a farm?
My uncle has one in Dholpur.
How does that matter?
What does he grow?
Sugarcane.
Okay.
Perfect.
So basically John and Summer want
to grow their sugarcane in your farm.
Do they want a sugarcane
or a baby?
Sugarcane = baby.
Carry on.
Summer's land is barren.
She will take your farm on rent.
John will plant the seed.
Summer will provide
the necessary manure.
You will hand over the sugarcane
to them as soon as it is ready,
and they'll pay you rent
for using your farm.
Your womb.. Their child...
So I won't have to sleep with anyone?
No.
- And I'll give birth to a baby?
- Yes.
You don't say!
Science has surely made
a lot of progress.
Is that really happening? For real?
Yes.
A lot of people do it.
That's what I have been
trying to explain to you.
Right.
So I need to carry their
baby in my womb for nine months.
You got it.
Have you lost your freaking mind?
Why on earth would I do that?
I want to be a movie star
and he wants me to become a mother.
There are so many women
in this country,
go find someone else.
Crazy man.
Zip it!
No crying!
Get him to shut up.
Crazy woman.
Mimi ji, you'll get 2 million for it.
2 million.
You want to go to Bollywood, right?
Isn't that what you prayed for?
It's a sign from God.
2 million.
Mom, does it hurt a lot,
while giving birth?
It hurts more
when your child strays away.
'Mimi ji, you'll get 2 million for it.'
'You want to go to Bollywood, right?'
'Isn't that what you prayed for?'
'It's a sign from God.'
'2 million.'
Stop bullshitting me.
This is what that guy said.
He's a nutcase.
Don't pay any heed to him.
It is quite common these days.
Girls are making millions
by renting out their wombs.
We cannot eat shit just
because someone else is.
Because we have a grand feast
laid out for us, right?
Don't just look at the
money that's being offered.
Give some thought to
what you have to do.
What should I do?
Jolly called,
asking when I'm coming to Bombay.
What should I tell him?
You know PC, Bebo, Kangana...
They were also surrogates?
No, they became actresses
at a very young age.
And I am already 25!
Any longer and I'll have
to play a mother instead.
I need to become a mother now,
to avoid to playing one on screen.
Think about it, Shama.
It's a lot of money.
Hard cash.
Give it another thought.
I am tired of dancing for peanuts.
All I am asking you to do
is meet the couple.
If we don't like it, we'll refuse.
Good Lord, he is so handsome.
I wouldn't mind sleeping
with him to have his baby.
Yes, he is hot.
Look at his eyes!
He is hot, but he won't sleep
with you, he's my husband.
What the hell!
Hindi... you speak?
I forgot to mention,
she speaks quite well.
She also knows the Gayatri
Mantra and Hanuman Chalisa.
Stop exaggerating.
I am not that good at it.
Good.
So tell me, the woman who gives
birth to your baby gets 2 million?
Yes.
And we like you.
Why her?
Why not someone else?
Why do you want it to be her?
Because she is super fit.
She is healthy.
And she's a dancer.
Athletes and dancers,
they have the best bodies.
Such ladies give birth
to healthy children.
Best body.
That's why.
Mimi ji, if you have
any questions for them,
about the baby, about the method,
then please go ahead.
Right.
In how many instalments
do I get my 2 million?
So, we've decided we'll give 50,000
every month for the first nine months.
And the rest - 1,550,000,
after the delivery.
1,550,000 in one shot, hard cash?
You betcha! Crisp bank notes!
You two can sleep on a bed of money.
One more thing.
If I have twins,
do I get paid double?
- No.
Why "no"?
No, you won't.
Double babies, double pain.
And if I have triplets like Farah Khan?
Then tripple?
What's she saying?
- Well, she's saying--
- She's saying two babies, money double.
Three babies, money triple.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Mimi listen, if that happens
of course we'll pay you more.
But please, I'm begging you,
don't give us more than two.
We can't afford it.
Come on now,
as if thats in my hands.
One more thing.
We will have to take you
to a clinic in Jaipur for a check-up.
So, it'll be great if you can
let us know your decision quickly?
If you aren't ready to do this
then we'll have to find another girl.
We'll be paying her then.
Aah.
"Neither wife,
nor kids, nor parents, nothing matters."
"The whole thing is that...
money rules over everything."
All things said and done,
what will I tell my family about the baby?
I'll start showing in a couple of months.
I can't say that I have gained weight.
They won't buy it.
You don't need to tell them anything.
- What do you mean?
I mean many surrogate
mothers stay away from home.
Many don't tell their parents.
You too could stay away from home.
Now don't ask me to find you a place.
Find your own place.
Where can I go?
Well, you can stay with me.
I stay quite far away from your place.
You don't have a family?
It's just me and my dad.
My dad is hardly home.
I don't get to see
him for months myself.
Why?
He's a Maulvi
He barely steps out of a mosque.
And I cannot step inside it.
It's the best solution... for you.
Think about it.
It's the best solution.
"Money rules over everything."
The technique of IVF,
removes several fertile eggs
From the ovaries,
for fertilization in the laboratory
Doctor, this is the
girl we were talking about.
So you are Mimi?
You don't say!
Aren't you on FB?
Have you willingly agreed to do this?
No one can dare force me.
Mimi ji, you'll have to keep a few things
in mind after you get pregnant.
You'll have to eat healthy.
You'll have to go on walks.
You'll have to stay happy and exercise--
Yes, yes.
Don't worry.
I'll carry the baby to term, hand
it over to them and collect my payment.
Money?
Do you have any doubts?
No.
Will I get stretch marks?
I mean, I hope it won't ruin my figure.
No.
- Have you gone through this?
- No.
So?
Has it ruined Shilpa Shetty's figure?
You don't say!
She is right.
Best body.
Mr. John, to start with
we will need your sperms.
Needhi will guide you
to the sperm deposit room.
Okay.
Sir?
If you need any help, call me?
That's kind of you, Bhanu.
I've done this before.
So Mrs. Summer, when was your last period?
"This is the best news of my life."
"It has made my heart rejoice."
"This means..."
"A guest is going to come."
"Its time to celebrate."
- "This means..."
- I am going to be the mother of your child!
"A guest is going to come."
"This means..."
"I have hit a jackpot."
"It's time to bid farewell
to regrets and welcome good luck."
"God has been generous."
"My prayers have been answered."
"Everything seems fragrant."
"Everywhere there are celebrations."
"My happiness knows no bounds."
Congratulations.
Huh?
The pregnancy strip was right.
She's pregnant.
Congratulations.
Oh, my God!
I love you.
Congratulations.
We're gonna be a mom and dad.
I love you so much.
Oh!
Mimi, thank you.
You've changed our lives.
- Thank you so much.
- Welcome.
No, not welcome.
Bhanu, you too, thank you so much.
- 2 million!
- No problem, sir.
Cash okay, cheque okay, no tax.
Yes, yes, of course.
Of course, don't worry about it.
Don't worry.
We did it.
Doctor, thank you.
Most welcome.
I'll see you soon?
We are so happy, Mimi.
Then how about making me happy as well?
- Yes!
- Oh!
- Yes, yes.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Mimi, this is for you.
- No.
- Hey!
- For her.
- Yeah.
This is for you.
Thank you.
And this is for the next four months.
We'll pay you the rest after we come back.
- Come back?
- Where are you going?
We are going back to America.
We need to get back to work
since we're becoming parents.
Need the money, right?
Need the money.
Don't worry.
I'm around to make
sure you don't face any problems.
We are fine even if you don't!
We can manage on our own.
- We don't need him.
- No, no, no.
Bhanu is here to take care of you.
I'll always stay in touch with Bhanu.
So please, let him stay.
It's their flower
nurturing in your garden.
Let me do the job of the gardener, okay?
Take care. Sister.
Okay?
Come here.
What will you tell your parents?
We should go or we are
not going to make the flight.
- Okay?
- No problem, ma'am.
John sir, Summer ma'am, come.
A movie shoot?
For nine months?
For that long?
Seems like a very big movie.
It is, Mom.
It's four hours long.
Four hours?
What's the name of the movie?
- The name?
- Yes.
"Love in the middle of the sea."
In the middle of the sea, huh?
Right.
What will they do
in the middle of the sea?
Love.
- Love.
- I see.
Let me explain.
- We will be shooting on a big ship.
- Okay.
The ship will stay in the sea
for nine months while we keep filming.
Haven't they already made a similar movie,
where the ship sinks and everyone
dies in the end?
Huh?
No, no, no.
No one is dying in this movie.
No one is dying in this movie, Dad.
As soon as the ship docks,
the parents give them their blessings,
and the girl and the boy get married.
The end, happy ending.
Very good.
- Isn't it?
- It's a good story, isn't it?
No?
No.
You cannot go.
Why not?
No.
You don't need to do this.
Boys from decent families don't
like girls who work in the movies.
Mom, once I become a star,
Then I will pick and choose
the guy I want to marry.
- Is it?
- Of course.
And look at this!
They have already given me an advance.
They are going pay me handsomely.
Think about it.
I'll be a movie star.
Huge posters of me everywhere.
I'll be on TV.
I'll do interviews.
Mine?
Of course,
they will interview you as well.
You'll be on TV as well.
Then I'll tell everyone how
great our art and our lineage is.
Yes, you should.
- Right?
- Right.
No.
Sit down.
Okay.
Mom!
Come on, just think about it.
We will renovate
our house every year.
Every year!
You'll be surrounded by servants.
Who will be forever at your command
Please let me do this.
Please let me go.
Don't ask me.
You and your father can do as you please.
Fine.
But only under one condition.
What condition?
You'll use your full name.
Mimi Maansingh Rathore.
Of course, I will!
Shama!
Salaam Alaikum. [Greetings]
Walaikum salaam. [Greetings]
Where are your guests from?
You know my aunt in Kalyan?
Your aunt in Kalyan?
The one who had grey
hair from a very young age?
Yes, I remember her.
The one who wears body
fitted dresses, right?
Right.
This is her niece.
Chand.
Salaam. [Greetings]
What did you say her name was?
- Chand.
And this is her husband.
Naseeruddin.
Salaam Walaikum. [Greetings]
Walaikum salaam. [Greetings]
What do you do?
I'm a driver.
With God's grace, I own my own car.
Praise Lord Ram
A second-hand car.
I have a new project underway.
Ill buy a new car soon.
- See you around.
- Okay.
Let me know if you
have contacts at the bank.
Sure. Always happy to help.
We are family.
Family always helps each other.
[Prayers]
Hey!
Morning walk!
Get up!
Come on guys!
Mimi... wakey-wakey.
Mimi, come on, wake up.
You are supposed to go on morning walks.
Come on, get up.
Let's do the morning walk in the evening.
Morning walk is good for the baby.
You don't do it, let the baby do it.
- Get up.
- But the baby wants to sleep.
Get up.
You look good.
Thanks.
Put this on.
Cover the whole face.
This okay?
Okay.
Salaam Alaikum, Shama. [Greetings]
Walaikum salaam. [Greetings]
Where are you off to
this early in the morning?
Just for a morning walk?
Chand is used to it.
Oh.
You didn't tell me that
Mimi is working in a movie?
- In a movie, huh?
- Yeah.
Mimi's father was telling
everyone at the bus depot.
She went to Mumbai to work in the movies.
She'll be a movie star soon.
I am sure you are aware about this.
Yes, she had told me about it.
Chand?
Let's go, Chand.
I have to say, Chand is quite tall.
She'll need 6 meters
of cloth at the least.
Right, anything less
won't suffice.
Hmm?
Who is it?
What...
Wait.
Fine, break the door.
Coming.
Who are you?
I am Shama's aunt's niece's husband.
But who are you?
- Who me?
- Yes.
Shama's father.
Oh that's wonderful,
I feel blessed with your presence.
It's so good to finally meet you.
Salaam walaikum. [Greetings]
Walaikum salaam. [Greetings]
Can I come in?
Sure.
Welcome to my house.
I mean welcome to your house.
I should quickly hide the alcohol.
What did you say your name was, mister?
- My name?
- Yes.
Nawazuddin.
- Nawazuddin?
- Yes.
So you are Zohra Begum's son-in-law?
Zohra?
No, I'm the son-in-law of the
aunt in Kalyan who wears tight dresses.
She is Zohra Begum.
Oh, her name is Zohra?
I didn't know.
I always addressed her as Mom.
Please forgive me, Mom.
Where is Shama?
Candle?
Extinguished it.
Why would we need it during the day?
I am talking about my daughter Shama.
She has gone out with my daughter--
my wife for morning walk.
- Walk?
- Yes.
Walk means using your
legs to move forward.
Let me show you.
This is what you'd call a slow walk.
This is a fast walk.
Come here, mister.
Please come here.
I know what "walk" means.
What I meant was what made
Shama suddenly go on a walk?
My wife is used to going on morning walks.
Doctor has advised it too.
One should go on walks regularly.
It's good for the heart.
Do you read Namaaz [Prayers]?
Yes, of course I do.
I read it quite often. I love it.
How many times do you read it?
10 times.
One reads Namaaz only
five times in day, mister.
I gave you a count for two days.
Did you read the Morning Namaaz
for the day?
I'll read it after I have a bath.
It is read at five in the morning.
I'll read it tomorrow morning at five.
Oh good lord, this guy...!
I'm a heart patient.
Can I lie down for a bit?
My heart's palpitating.
Yes, of course.
You should rest.
Look at him, he's still sleeping.
- Shama.
- Dad!
Thank God you came.
When did they come?
You remember the aunty from Kalyan?
Who wears tight dresses?
Why does everyone keep telling
me about the way she dresses!
No?
I asked, when did they get here.
Yesterday.
This is Chand.
Salaam. [Greetings]
She is pregnant.
Okay.
She was just a baby
when she had come here.
Do you remember?
You don't talk to anyone,
so you don't know anything.
Well, she was finding it difficult
at her house so I asked her to come here.
Dad, I did the right thing, didn't I?
Yes, you did the right thing.
This must be God's will.
- Right.
- Zohra Begum has done a lot for us.
You go have a bath,
then accompany me to the Mosque.
We'll read the Afternoon Namaaz there.
"Hey Sparkler,"
"You have been acting all weird."
[Background vocal]
"Sometimes, you are like
slippery dew drops on a flower."
a gum that gets stuck to the gums."
"Hey Sparkler..."
"Don't knock at the
door of my heart so hard."
[Background vocal]
"You are a mystery,"
"Oh Sparkler..."
"You are a hormonal mess."
"Everything you do is so absurd."
"Oh Sparkler..."
"Hey Sparkler,"
"You look like a fish
Out of water."
"Why is your temper as unpredictable
as the share market?"
"Sometimes you crave for tamarind."
"And sometimes for chillies."
"And sometimes like Devdas's Paro,
"Oh Sparkler..."
"And sometimes like Chandramukhi,"
"Why so sad? Come on give me a smile,"
"Oh Sparkler..."
"Hey Sparkler,"
"You have been acting all weird."
Oh!
Look at you!
You look more
beautiful than before, Mimi.
Right?
Want to see something fun?
Touch here.
Oh.
Feel.
Oh, do you feel it?
That's our baby.
I've never felt anything like that before.
Make us also feel like never before.
Huh?
Oh.
We have something for him, right?
Oh yeah, yeah.
That's our baby.
Bhanu.
Mimi...
Yeah.
I'm sure its are all there.
Doctor? Doctor?
Okay, yeah.
Good.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
I have put on some weight, haven't I?
- No?
- Good take care, sir.
You've done a great job.
[Folk music]
You're gonna be a great dad.
You're gonna be a great mom.
Oh.
Hey, Doctor.
Hello.
Please sit.
Okay.
We had some doubts
after the last check-up,
so we did a battery
of tests on Mimi yesterday.
What's wrong, Doctor?
There is a problem with your child.
Your child is mentally challenged.
Your child has down syndrome.
What?
That's what the reports say.
I'm-- I'm really very sorry.
I know it's very hard for you
to accept it, but it happens sometimes.
No matter how much care you
take of yourself or your child,
your child turns out to be disabled.
Can't you fix it, Doctor?
What any hospital can do is provide
you with medical care and a specialist--
Summer, wait.
Wait, Doctor.
Summer!
John, let's go.
Listen, listen--
Please John, let's just go.
Babe, we can make this work.
No.
No, I can't.
We don't need this baby, John.
Please, let's just go home.
Please, let's go home.
What's wrong, Summer ji?
What happen?
Bhanu, take us to Mimi.
What?
No, no, no, I can't.
I can't face her, John.
Please no.
No.
- I can't.
- What happen?
What happen?
Bhanu, pull over.
No.
You don't want the baby?
Have you lost it?
You think this is a game?
Bhanu.
We can't raise this child.
You think money can
buy you everything, right?
You think this is a poor country,
just throw some cash and
we will do anything?
No.
Bhanu that is not how we think.
We have been touring India for a year now.
We have visited many surrogacy clinics.
You know why?
Because-- because we
wanted a perfect surrogate,
so that we get a perfect
and a healthy baby.
Not a disabled one.
Not-- not a baby with down syndrome.
What will we do with such a child, Bhanu?
And what will that
girl do with that child?
It is your baby.
You have to keep it, no matter how it is.
My wife and I would've treasured
the child if it had been ours.
Bhanu, please understand.
We can't raise a disabled baby.
We just can't.
We can't.
Don't ask us to keep this baby.
I request you.
Please tell Mimi...
to get rid of the baby.
- I can't.
- Please don't say that.
No.
- Summer ji?
- No.
John sir?
Sir, I request you.
I request you, please take your baby.
Take your baby.
This isn't what we wanted, Bhanu.
I'll find you a place in Juhu,
that's where all the movie stars stay.
Right.
Find a nice house.
It should be sea facing.
- Sea facing?
- Yes.
You know how expensive it will be?
You don't say!
You don't need to worry about the money,
Jolly Brother.
Shama and I will be
there in a couple of months.
Listen, let's make Shama
sing in our viral video, yeah?
She is a great singer.
You should have a word with Bhushan ji.
I'll talk to him and get back to you.
Okay.
Don't forget to send
me pictures of the house.
Right.
Okay, bye.
Bhanu!
You too should come to Mumbai with us.
You can be my driver.
We will have loads of fun, right?
Right.
What's wrong?
Why this sad face?
What happened?
Summer ji said that
she doesn't want the baby.
What do you mean by
she doesn't want the baby?
Are you high or what?
Doctor's reports state that
there is a problem with the child.
Problem?
What's the problem?
- What's wrong?
- I don't know.
She has asked you to abort the child.
Abort the child?
Have you lost it, Bhanu?
Are you out of your mind?
- Let me call Summer.
- How can she say that?
She is carrying their child, Bhanu.
I cannot get through.
They agreed to this.
We did this for them.
How can she say that?
I cannot get through her phone!
Where is Summer?
I just dropped them to their hotel.
Get out of my way.
Mimi!
Shama she will run away.
Hurry up.
Hurry up, Bhanu.
Where are John and Summer?
They just checked out and left.
They left?
Where did they go?
Mimi!
[Indistinct Chatter]
What have you done!
What kind of a movie
were you shooting for?
I told you not to send her.
But you wouldn't listen to me.
Now make her use her full name!
Shama, you have committed
a sin by hiding this from us.
We treated you like our own
daughter and you betrayed us.
This is how you repay
him for teaching you everything?
What did you tell us, Mimi?
"I'll make my family proud, Dad."
"Everyone will learn about our art."
You have destroyed our family's name.
You have ruined everything,
my art, my honour, my reputation.
You have broken my trust.
Come on, tell me!
Tell me who the father is!
Tell me, who is the
man you got married to, huh?
Don't tell me you didn't get married.
I will die of shame.
I'll set this house on
fire along with everything else.
I'll set everything on fire.
Who is the father, Mimi?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Tell me, who is the father?
Tell us.
- Tell me!
- He!
He?
Me?
You got me into all this.
You are the one who convinced
me to have this baby.
Why did you listen to him?
He is old enough to be your father!
No.
I am nowhere close to your age.
I am just 38 years old.
How can he be Mimi's husband?
He's a Muslim.
Huh?
- He's a Muslim?
- He's a Muslim!
Oh, my God!
A Muslim?
Oh God, this is a disaster.
What have you done!
I've seen him with his wife.
His wife?
That was his aunt, not his wife.
Listen, I am not a Muslim
and I don't have a wife.
Hang on.
Here.
Age: 42 years.
Read my name first.
All you can see is my age, huh?
Bhanupratap Pandey.
He's a Hindu.
That was a close shave, Aunt.
That was a close shave, indeed.
Shobha, you should end this drama now.
Our daughter is pregnant.
You should look after her.
Maansingh, you are the
one who should be blamed for this.
Why did you let her go alone, huh?
Anyway, we cannot change the past.
You need to take special care of her now.
She is expecting a child.
You will be grandparents.
Mimi, you too should stop crying.
Don't cry, my child.
Wipe your tears, come on.
You should eat something.
You should not stay
hungry during a pregnancy.
Come on, get up.
Come on.
What will you have?
Should I make you your favourite meal?
Would you like to have it?
Come on, my child.
Why doesn't Mimi dress
up like a married woman?
Perhaps he doesn't inspire
her to dress up like a married woman?
So, do you have a house of your own,
or you plan to stay here with us?
This is not right, Mimi ji!
I have a mother,
a wife and a house in Delhi.
Why did you get me into this mess?
You rascal!
I got you into a mess, huh?
I got you into a mess
or was it vice-versa?
What had you told me, huh?
"You should do it, Mimi ji."
"It's just a matter of nine months."
"All your dreams will come true."
"They are very nice people."
Nice, my foot!
They are nice people, huh?
"John ji! Summer ji!"
What happened, huh?
Where are they now, huh?
Where are they?
They ran away!
Leaving me alone with this baby!
What example had you given me, huh?
"You just need to grow
their sugarcane in your farm."
I want to shove all
those sugarcanes up yours!
Say something, Bhanupratap Pandey.
You better take care of
this baby once its born.
I won't keep it.
Got it?
You've ruined my life.
Why did I listen to you?
You should go to Mumbai.
Become an actor.
I'll take care of the baby.
And what will you tell people?
Where were these people when my
husband divorced me?
Don't worry.
I'll handle it.
Aatif?
Yes?
Mimi's husband--
Your son-in-law?
Right.
When do you think they met?
When did they get married?
He must've bamboozled Mimi
during one of her dance performances.
I don't see her falling in
love with a two-bit driver otherwise.
Hmm.
He must have done some black magic on her.
Mimi!
Shobha!
- What's wrong?
I don't know what's wrong.
It just hurts a lot.
You are in pain?
What's wrong?
Let's take her to the doctor.
I'll go call the neighbourhood doctor.
Yes, call him.
No, her doctor is in Jaipur.
She knows her case quite well.
We will have to go there.
Wear this, dear.
Come on, my child.
Take your time.
Be careful.
I'll come with you.
No!
You guys stay here.
We'll go there alone.
Right, no one will come with us.
Shut up!
We will all go with her.
Right, we will all go with her.
We've had enough.
We are done listening to you.
Let's go.
Calm down.
Take deep breaths.
- Drive faster.
- Okay.
Ouch!
Watch it.
Huh?
Relax, my baby, try to relax.
It stopped.
It stopped?
What stopped?
The pain.
- The pain stopped?
- Yes, it stopped.
She is no longer in pain.
- You are feeling okay?
- Turn the car around.
Home?
Take us home.
- I am feeling better.
- Okay.
It stopped.
Relax, relax.
- It stopped, right?
- Yes.
It stopped?
- Take us home.
- Okay.
Mimi, are you feeling okay now?
Ouch!
What happened?
It's back! It's back! It's back!
The pain is back.
It's back.
- Turn the car around.
- Turn the car around, hurry up.
Turn the car around.
Why don't you drive?
No, you drive.
It takes time.
It'll all be good.
It's all good. It's all good.
- It'll all be good.
- Right.
Come.
Follow me.
Doctor!
- She is in a lot of pain.
- Yes.
Where's the mother?
What do you mean by where's the mother?
She is carrying the baby,
so isn't it obvious that she's the mother?
Are you sure she's a doctor?
She's the surrogate.
Huh?
Rubbish.
She is Mimi.
Or did you change your name as well?
Surrogate means...
Doctor, it's hurting really bad.
Please examine her quickly.
Nurse, take her inside.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
All of you wait here.
No, we will go with her.
The doctor has asked us to wait here,
all of us.
Let her go.
No, no, no.
- No one is allowed in there.
- Mimi?
False labour pains.
It's known as Braxton-Hicks contractions.
It is very common during
this time of pregnancy.
Where is Summer?
She ran away,
because you told her that
there is some problem with this baby.
Oh God, why do people do such things?
How many times has this
happened before, Doctor?
In the past few years,
in many surrogacy cases,
parents have refused to accept the baby.
They run away, especially the foreigners.
In such cases,
most of the girls abort the child.
Doctor, from what I have felt,
I believe that the
child inside me is alive.
It grows, it breathes,
it eats, it moves.
I think it can also hear us.
Then why is it ok to kill
a baby on the inside,
When it is a crime on the outside?
Why don't people accept the
child inside?
Irrespective of its condition.
A child is a child right?
Hmm?
"You seem..."
"Like..."
"Yourself..."
"But this..."
"Is not you..."
"Your face..."
"smiles,"
"But it doesn't reach..."
"your eyes,"
"Who'd understand..."
"your pain?"
Who will set you free?"
"Set you free..."
"Why did your aspirations..."
"End..."
"All your desires..."
"are locked away?"
"All your dreams..."
"fade away..."
"And are wiped clean"
"The waves dont reach the shore"
"They are upset..."
"Who'd understand..."
"your pain?"
"Who will set you free?"
"Set you free..."
Can I ask you something?
You know that you got me into this mess.
But even if you ran away.
What could I do?
I wouldn't have
followed you to Delhi.
And even if I did,
you could have easily refused to help me.
This is not your child.
So why are you still here?
I am a driver, Mimi ji.
We have some principles.
The passenger must always
reach his destination...
There may be bad roads,
potholes, even accidents,
but that doesn't give me
an excuse to leave them stranded.
Okay listen,
if you experience any
pain during the night,
then hit me with this bottle.
You are anyway an expert
at throwing things.
I have a request,
please don't start screaming.
My heart starts sinking
and I start feeling scared.
Hmm?
I won't scream.
Okay.
Good night.
What's wrong?
Labour pains!
I'm getting the car.
Get ready,
we'll have to go to Jaipur.
Jaipur is too far away.
She'll end up having the baby in the car.
Let's take her to the
Government Hospital instead.
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Madam!
She is in lot of pain.
Excuse me, its an emergency.
Let's go.
Wait here.
Wait here, all of you.
Hey...
She is in so much pain.
Sit down.
Please sit down.
Shama?
Mimi is in labour.
We are at the local hospital.
Come quickly.
What happened?
We need you to sign here.
Who me?
Yes, you.
You are the father, right?
Yes, he is.
We didn't have much of a choice.
Sign it.
I am about to become a father
for the first time. I am so happy.
My father had become
a grandfather at your age.
We are against child marriages.
Push when you feel the pain coming, okay?
Take deep breaths.
What's happening?
They've forbidden us from going in there.
Can't I just--
Sit down.
Yes, yes, yes. Relax.
Yes, yes, yes.
Calm down, calm down.
We are almost there.
- Relax, relax.
- I can't do it.
You can do it.
- You can do it.
- I can't do it.
Very good. You can do it.
Push when you feel the pain coming, okay?
Take deep breaths.
One more push, come on.
Yes, yes, yes.
We are almost there.
Calm down, calm down.
Relax, relax.
Push when you feel the pain coming, okay?
I can't do it.
You can do it.
Take deep breaths. One more push.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can do it.
Yes.
Very good.
Push.
One more push.
Yes.
She came.
Congratulations.
It's a boy.
Thank God.
Both mother and child are doing well.
Thank you, Lord.
This is great.
Can we go meet them?
Of course,
you can, but only after some time.
Okay.
It's a boy!
Doctor?
Yes?
Is the child normal?
Yes, he is.
Why do you ask?
Previous tests showed that
there was a problem with the child.
There was a problem?
What was the problem?
- Where did you do these tests?
- In Jaipur.
There is a possibility that
the test might have suggested a problem.
But these tests are not always accurate.
Sometimes the tests
show incorrect results.
They are known as false positives.
Don't worry.
This baby is absolutely fine.
He is quite fair,
don't you think?
Yes, he is.
He has taken after his dad.
I have to say, I have never
seen such a beautiful child in my life.
You have given me such a lovely grandson.
No one in the city
has such a beautiful child.
I forgive you for all your mistakes.
Where's the baby?
Here.
Is this Mimi's child?
You think they left
someone else's child here?
Hmm?
- Uncle?
- Hmm?
- Uncle--
- Get your hand off me.
I think Mimi has tricked this driver.
I think the father
is someone else.
Hey!
No.
Mimi doesn't look like
uncle's daughter either.
Right.
Zip it.
Don't touch him.
Shut up.
Aatif, click our picture
with the baby?
This way.
Smile.
What did Mimi do so different
that she had such a beautiful child?
She ate fabric chalk.
Morning walk.
Look at them!
Going crazy over a fair baby.
They are here.
Look, such a fair baby!
Stay back, everyone.
"Fair baby! Fair baby!"
Buzz off!
When will this country
Stop obsessing over colour!
Let me ward off the evil.
You can enter the house
only after I am done.
Let me have a look at him.
You never stop amazing us, Lord.
He's like a lotus blooming in muddy water.
Mud?
Come on,
let's take our lotus inside.
Let's go.
He has become a star.
His mother is also a star.
Right.
- Here, feed him.
- Again?
You can stay.
She is your wife.
I am allergic.
Allergic?
To breast milk?
Feed him 10 times a day.
I'll go make something healthy for you.
How do you feel?
I don't know.
I feel different.
I had never imagined this.
What we imagine is not life!
What happens to us, is Life.
I had never imagined that
I'd lose mom so early in life.
Or that dad would
choose a spiritual life.
Or that the man I'd marry
would turn out to be a monster.
But what can we do?
We have to keep moving forward.
Hmm.
I guess you are right.
So, what have you decided?
What's next?
Next?
Change his diaper.
Bhanu, what's your secret
behind having such a fair child?
Please share it with me.
Promise you won't tell anyone?
Boil red soil with a
pinch of salt and drink it.
- Really?
- Really.
Have it twice a day.
And if you manage to get a strand of
white goat's beard, is magical!
- A white goat's beard?
- Yes.
Thanks, bro.
Hi Rekhu!
What is wrong with you?
Why aren't you taking my calls?
I told you I am busy.
I am traveling with the American couple.
Are you showing
them the whole country?
You remember you have a family, don't you?
Of course I do,
that's why I sent some money.
Didn't I come there just a few days back?
Even took you sightseeing.
What else do you want?
How's Mom?
Mom?
Mom misses you.
She keeps crying.
Hello?
Yes?
Come back, son.
I am missing you.
I will come back soon.
People who go to Mumbai don't
come back for years at a stretch.
I keep visiting you, don't I?
Why do you even bother?
Why don't you go abroad
with that couple?
Hang up now.
Hello?
You want to know how to have
a fair baby too right?
Eat turmeric.
And drink half a glass of milk,
and use the other half to wash off.
Every day.
Something is not right, Mom.
It's been months since he last came home.
He could have come at least once.
What's wrong with this American couple,
they don't seem to want to go back.
I think I should talk to Altaf.
Uncle, my brother in Saudi had called.
There's a job opening at his hotel.
He wants me there.
After learning music for 10 years,
you want to work in a hotel?
I can't help it. I'll have to go.
Very good.
Go.
When you go there,
find me a suitable job as well.
Sure, Uncle. I will find
you one as soon as I get there.
Have you seen him?
Him?
Who hasn't seen him?
No one is as lucky as he is.
You know him?
He is Mimi's husband.
Mimi's husband?
Who is Mimi?
He's Mimi's husband?
He is Rekha's husband.
Let's go, Mom.
Have you lost it?
Want another smack?
What is this lunatic saying?
Your delicious meals
remind me of my mother.
One day I'll make you meet her.
Does Mimi stay here?
Yes.
You are Mimi?
Who are you?
What do you want?
What's wrong with you?
Why did you marry my husband?
Any boy would have happily
married you.
Stop your nonsense.
I think you've got the wrong house.
Where do you think you are going, huh?
God cant save you today!
Dont you dare hide in the temple.
Come with me.
Come on.
Why!
Why did you do this, huh?
Don't you have any shame?
You have no shame?
Why did you do this, huh?
Why?
You left your wife for this young witch?
- Wife?
- What?
- His wife?
- Yes.
Oh God, what is going on?
Son-in-law?
Is it true?
He is not your son under any law.
She is his wife.
And he is my son.
Who are you guys, huh?
Son?
What is going on, Shobha?
What are they saying, huh?
He's a married man!
How many more secrets
does your movie have, Mimi?
Start talking, you wretch.
You left your wife for this young girl?
I hope you at least remember
this old mother of yours.
Rekha!
Rekhu, please hear me out.
I don't want to hear a word.
My life has been ruined.
Rekhu...
Is she really your wife?
I cannot believe that two
women are fighting over this driver.
He has a genie under his command, Uncle.
Hello, he has no genie under his command.
I am his wife.
His first and official wife.
Are you the burqa clad
woman I'd seen with him?
A burqa clad woman? Mom?
Oh God! You have a Muslim wife as well?
Didn't I tell you that she was his aunt?
His aunt?
But I don't have a sister.
Who was that woman?
Why don't you tell us, huh?
There you go!
Bastard! You were already married?
How dare you marry my
daughter have a child with her!
- A child!
- Yes.
- His child?
Oh hell!
This is a nightmare!
He had a child with her?
That's why he left you, Rekha.
He had a child with this tall witch
because he couldn't have one with you.
Where's his child?
Is that his child?
Easy! Easy...
He is asleep.
Whose child is he?
He is my child.
Who is his father?
Your husband.
Let me have a look at him.
What is this?
This is Bhanu's child?
Mimi please tell them the
truth before someone ends up dead.
I am not going to die!
But I will take your
dead body back with us!
Where do you think you
are running to, huh?
You gave her such a beautiful child?
And all I got was hope.
He is not the father.
There!
Huh?
And I am not married to him.
What do you mean by
you are not married?
What are you saying?
I don't understand.
Tell me the truth.
Shama, why don't you
tell us the truth, hmm?
An American couple had come here.
They had their child
planted inside Mimi's womb.
They promised her a huge sum
if she'd carry their baby to term.
But they didn't keep
their word and they ran away.
They ran away?
How can they just plant
their child in her womb?
She must have done something
with that American man...
No Mom, she didn't.
This is a new technology.
He is their child.
She just nurtured him in her womb.
- Oh God!
- I didnt, I swear.
She isn't married.
She didn't become a movie star.
She isn't his mother.
I am feeling dizzy.
Aatif, get me some water.
And put some poison in it.
Mimi,
you gave birth to this child, right?
Yes, Mom.
So you are his mother, right?
I am his mother.
And he belongs to us.
He is your grandson.
He is our Raj.
Right.
"Life's a mystery,
don't try to figure it out."
"Life's a journey, just enjoy the ride."
"It's a new dawn."
"It's a new day."
"Our destination will
always remain the same,"
"only the paths will change."
"Life's a mystery,
don't try to figure it out."
"Life's a journey, just enjoy the ride."
Mimi, Bunty teased me at school.
He called me a white ghost.
Why am I so different
from the others, Mimi?
Bunty has no sense.
Don't pay attention to him.
You are not an ordinary child.
You see that star?
You were a star just like that one.
- Then?
- Then what?
A white angel came and gifted you to me.
He is very smart.
He is very naughty.
And he... will have a lot of chocolates.
You don't say!
I didn't know that, Mimi.
I didn't know that!
"The ones you've been
humming since ages..."
"If not the lyric, atleast..."
"Change the melody of those songs"
"It takes aways so much"
"Yet returns in so many folds."
"They say,
time takes pleasure in doing so"
"Life's a mystery,
don't try to figure it out."
"Life's a journey, just enjoy the ride."
"It's a new dawn."
"It's a new day."
"Our destination will
always remain the same,"
"only the paths will change."
"Life's a mystery,
don't try to figure it out."
"Life's a journey, just enjoy the ride."
"Life's a mystery,
don't try to figure it out."
"Life's a journey, just enjoy the ride."
Mimi, why did you name me Raj?
Because that's what heroes
are called in the movies.
You are the hero of my movie, aren't you?
Where's my heroine, Mimi?
What do you mean where is she?
Who am I then?
Mimi.
You don't say!
I didn't become a heroine because of him,
and he won't even let
me be the star in his life.
No one values
talent and sacrifice here.
One... Two...
Hey you naughty boy Raj.
Mimi you lost!
Grandma! I won!
Grandma, who are these people?
Hi.
Look at you.
This is not fair.
You cheat every day.
Raj, go to your room.
Ok Mimi.
I'm sorry.
I'm so so sorry.
Please forgive me.
Please, I am sorry.
I'm so glad you kept our baby.
My baby.
Mimi, this woman saying
that Raj is her son.
How dare you say that he is your son, huh?
Don't you have any shame?
How dare you come back
after four years and say that?
Mimi--
Mimi, we're so very-very sorry.
- Sorry?
- Yeah.
Please, just...
give us a chance to explain.
Mimi, after we left, we didn't try
to have another baby through surrogacy.
Please, we were quite disturbed.
We were just trying to
be happy for all this time.
One day, we saw a video on Facebook.
We saw a white boy dancing
with his Indian mother in a hotel.
We realised that the mother is you.
Yes, mother is me not you!
Okay?
You ran away.
Because you thought
that your child is faulty.
There is no fault in the child.
Your way of thinking is faulty.
The problem lies with you.
You left your child in
someone's womb and ran away.
You didn't even think about me.
What will I do?
What will happen to the child?
You'd asked me to abort the child, right?
And suddenly, after four years,
you realised that you love your child?
You think you are "mother-father" of Raj?
No!
No.
I am "mother-father" of Raj.
I gave birth to him.
I nurtured him.
I raised him, not you.
Got it?
Why are you here?
What do you want?
Our baby.
Don't even think about it.
Don't you dare think about it!
Get out.
Please forgive me.
Mimi!
Mimi look at this!
This is our house.
This is me.
That's you.
That's Bhanu.
Aunt Shama.
And grandma grandpa.
What's wrong, Mimi?
Nothing.
You didn't like my drawing?
Your drawing is perfect.
Then whats the problem?
You'll never leave your Mimi, right?
Never.
Promise?
Promise.
How can they just ask
us to give the child back?
How dare they come back!
They think this is a joke?
Why didn't you slap her?
Shameless woman!
Like he is some toy,
that they left behind
and now want back.
They have no right over the child.
If they cause trouble, don't worry...
I am friends with a few cops.
We have brought some toys for Raj.
From the US.
I have personally bought them.
We don't want them!
Why are you back?
Mimi, please understand.
We have faced a lot.
I too have faced a lot.
Please, please listen.
Raj is our last hope.
You can have another child.
But I can't.
Raj will be happy with us.
You became a surrogate
For a brighter future, Mimi.
What will you do for Raj's future, huh?
We'll give him the best life in US.
- You--
- Mimi!
Mimi!
Hi!
Hey!
I hear your name is Raj.
My name is John.
This is Summer.
Hi!
Auntie, are these for me?
Yes.
We brought them for you.
Look at this.
Look.
So many toys!
Aeroplane!
Remote Control!
See...
It can fly.
Auntie, are you the same white
angel who had left me with Mimi?
Yes.
That's me.
Raj, come with me.
You need to get ready for school.
Mimi let me go.
I don't have school today, Mimi.
Please let him play.
Look it flies!
Thank you, Mimi.
I feel so alive being around him.
Angel Auntie?
It has stopped working.
Okay.
Wait.
Let me help.
There you go.
I swear Mimi, I haven't seen
Summer this happy in four years.
Enough of this drama.
Raj isn't your child.
He is Mimi's son.
No Bhanu, he isn't.
Look at him.
Look.
You think he belongs here?
No.
He's our son and we're
not going back without him.
You don't know this, but Summer tried to--
Summer attempted suicide.
Now do you want her
to die because I don't.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
And I will go to any extent
for my wife's happiness.
So, give me my son back or
I will take legal action against you.
Do you understand?
Raj!
You...!
You just wait there, you scoundrel.
Are you blind?
Can't you see?
- You couldn't see my baby?
- Mimi! Mimi!
What if something would
have happened to him?
He was playing in the middle of the road.
- So what?
- He was playing on the road.
- He can play wherever he wants.
- Let him go.
He is my child.
Let him go, Mimi.
He was playing on the road.
Who are you to tell me where
he can play and cannot play?
Please go.
- Buzz off.
- Go.
- Come on, Mimi.
- Let's go inside, Mimi.
John ji.
Summer ji.
I am sorry to learn
what you have been through.
I heard you tried to commit suicide.
Summer ji, sometimes it
is easier to die than to survive.
You two left her in that state,
but Mimi still survived and she fought.
She fought with herself,
with the society and her dreams.
It has been a long,
uphill battle for her.
You know she wanted
to be a movie star.
She is the most beautiful
girl in Shekhawati.
She is the best dancer we have here.
She wanted to go to Mumbai
and join the film industry.
After Raj was born,
she bundled up all her dreams,
and threw them somewhere
far away in the desert.
Raj is her world now.
And now you came and take legal action?
Listen Bhanu--
Listen, listen John,
you think Mimi is alone?
No.
We are with her.
You can go anywhere you want,
approach any court you want.
We are ready to fight.
Let's go.
Mimi?
The angel is back to take her star.
How do I fight an angel, Shama?
This contract clearly states that you need
to hand over the child after the delivery,
if they pay you what
they had agreed upon.
You will have to handle
the child over to them.
But they ran away,
leaving the child with her.
That doesn't give Mimi
legal rights over the child.
They will do a DNA test and
prove their paternity in the court.
Bhanu, we can fight a case against them,
but it won't be easy.
It will be a long and
an expensive legal battle.
Mimi and the child will have to
be present in the court for every hearing.
Why does the child
need to go to the court?
The case won't move forward without him.
We are fighting this case for him.
I'll get going now.
Bhanu, let me know when the case is filed.
- Okay.
- We will try our best.
Okay.
I will walk you out.
Don't worry, Mimi.
You have our support.
You gave birth to him and
you are the one bringing him up.
So how can she be his mother?
Raj might look like a westerner,
but at heart he is an Indian,
just like us.
He speaks our language.
He eats our food.
So how can he belong to them?
I have told him that
we want to go ahead with it.
I'll sell my car if we
need money to fight the case.
We can also sell this house if required.
It is quite old.
We're just four of us.
We don't need such a big house.
Raj should go to America,
with John and Summer.
How can you say that, Mimi?
Don't let them beguile you.
Raj is your son.
It was my farm,
but the seed
and manure was theirs
Have you lost your mind?
Do you even know what you are saying?
I know, Mom.
I just needed
money to go to Mumbai.
It was Summer who wanted a child.
She was the one who wanted to be a mother.
I wanted to be a movie star.
What about me?
Have you ever thought about what I wanted?
I just wanted happiness and
Raj is the one who gave it to me.
He is my grandson.
You too considered him as
your son after you gave birth to him.
Not just you,
we all considered him as your son.
My wife says, "It's a good thing,
we don't have a child of our own."
"Raj doesn't have to compete
with anyone for our love."
We keep looking for excuses
to come and meet him.
He is the soul of this house.
We will go to any court we have to.
We will fight for him.
What will we gain from it, huh?
We will fight the case for
years but what will we prove by that?
That Raj isn't their child?
Anyone who sees Raj with Summer
and John will now that he is their child.
They will keep calling Raj to
court and bombard him with questions.
What will he say?
He is just a child.
No.
I don't want him to go through this.
Mimi, you have made many wrong decisions.
Don't make a wrong decision this time.
Our lives are at stake.
We cannot take a child
away from his mother, Dad.
Summer is his real mother, Mom.
Let her have him.
"Oh my little birdie,"
"Where are you going?"
"Why are you leaving your home?"
"Why are you leaving your family?"
"Why are you leaving your mother?"
"Oh my child,"
"Oh my little birdie,"
"Where are you going?"
Mimi!
Come here, my boy.
Mimi, why aren't you coming
with me in the aeroplane?
- I have a show.
- Yes.
You love my shows, don't you?
Yes, I love them.
I'll finish my show and join you, okay?
You know what you have to do until then?
I have to be nice to Aunt
Summer and play with Uncle John.
I have to be a good boy.
"Love is a strange thing."
"It is hard to comprehend."
"We won't hear you
play in the house again."
"But your presence will
still be felt everywhere."
"Our tears will stop one day,"
"but the void that we
feel will never go away."
We are going back.
Raj is your son, Mimi.
And thats my daughter, over there.
We drove past an orphanage.
There she was.
She was crying,
as though she was waiting for us.
She wanted a home and we wanted a child.
So we met the lawyer, we're adopting her.
Isn't she cute?
Summer ji, you are adopting her?
Yes.
Mimi,
I cant forcefully take Raj away from you
and be happy.
And what about Raj?
Will he be able to stay with me?
Without you?
That's not possible, Mimi.
You know what I realised
after I saw you with Raj?
That you don't need to give
birth to a child to be a parent.
And that you don't need to
have your own child to be a parent.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I'll love her just
as much as you love Raj.
Mimi,
we hope that we can raise our
little girl the way you raised Raj.
Hi!
Hello.
What is your name?
Tara.
Raj, say hello to Tara.
She is so cute.
Auntie, I want to go in an aeroplane.
Raj, just get into my
car and fasten your seatbelt,
I'll make my car fly like an aeroplane.
Your granny and your mom
can be your airhostesses.
Do you have any more questions?
Mimi, when someone pees in the aeroplane,
does it fall on the ground?
See you, Summer ji.
"They say..."
"They say what you give is yours..."
"Play..."
"In my lap my moonchild."
"In the middle of the
night I still think of you"
"I see you in my eyes,
how will I get through?"
"All I can say is I'm sorry"